## **Daniel Tiburcio Buarao**

I Hold a Bachelor of Science in Information Technology, with a Specializing in technical support for both hardware and software systems. In addition to my academic qualifications, I am deeply committed to web development and have acquired substantial experience in social media marketing and sales.

#### Buaraodaniel01@gmail.com 🔀

Daniel-Buarao in

\_\_\_\_

+639-452-044-809



https://danielbuarao.github.io/DBPortfolio/Portfolio.html

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Online Business I Self-Employed Puff deck

01/2023 - 05/2023

- Managing Business Page.
- Creating ads Design for promoting the Product
- Negotiate Contracts and Monitored Costumer Service quality.
- Researched market trends and identified opportunities for product development or expansion.

## **Technical Support Engineer** (On-the-job

*Training)* Tech Mahindra 08/2023 - 11/2023

- Solving Computer tech issue for the Staff members.
- Setting up hardware and software.
- Managing and maintaining the computer system.
- Configuring TCP/IP Addressing using APIPA method.
- Perform troubleshooting of Lan and Connectivity issues.
- Perform Move station and setup.
  - Install, Support and diagnose Basic Application software for the Company such as Citrix, RTclient etc.

## **Property Consultant**

**DMCI** Homes

04/2024 - 09/2024

- Managing Business Page.
- Creating ads Design for promoting the Product
- Negotiate Contracts and Monitored Costumer Service quality.
  Digital Marketing

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

### **Web Development:**

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, REACT.

## **Computer Management Skills:**

Hardware Development, Analysis, and Testing Network Configuration, Technical Support and Troubleshooting.

#### Sales Skills:

Product Expertise, Negotiating, Social Media Selling.

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

Written and oral communication Attention to detail Public speaking

Peer collaboration

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Science in Information Technology** *ICCT COLLEGES*

2019 - 2023

## **Accountancy Business and**

Management Tañong High School

2013 - 2019

#### **CERTIFICATES AND LICENSES**

#### **CCNAv7: Introduction to Networks**

Cisco Networking Academy

**Udemy: Website Creation** 

Website Creation: Start learning from the beginning.

**Udemy: HTML** 

The Complete Guide to HTML for Beginners

#### **Udemy: JavaScript for Beginners**

The A-to-Z course to Mastering JavaScript

## **Udemy: HTML5 & CSS3 Complete**

Course Build Website like a Pro

#### **Udemy: JavaScript for Beginners Complete Course**

Learn JavaScript Programming Language with Practical Interaction.

#### **Udemy: Next.Js Web Dev: React Framework**

Next.Js Mastery: Harnessing React, Advanced Routing, Seamless API Integration, and web optimization Strategies